Guide to the Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 4. Office Administration Files, 1962-2010 TJU.2010.01.04
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Administrative Assistant Files, 1962-2010; I.
  - Patrick Meehan, 1984-1994; 23.
    - Election returns, Governor primary, 1994 (Box 621, Folder 68)
    - Employer Trip Reduction Program, 1994 (Box 621, Folder 69)
    - Employment Non-Discrimination Act, 1988-1991 (Box 621, Folder 70)
    - EPA, Newsclips, 1990-1991 (Box 621, Folder 71)
    - Ethics, Newsclips, 1991 (Box 621, Folder 72)
    - FAST, 1991-1993 (Box 621, Folder 73)
    - FAST, Trade bill, 1991 (Box 621, Folder 74)
    - Federal budget, Newsclips, 1990-1991 (Box 621, Folder 75)
    - FBI Office of Public and Congressional Affairs, 1993 (Box 621, Folder 76)
    - Federal judges, Newsclips, 1991-1992 (Box 621, Folder 77)
    - Firearm legislation, 1989-1993 (Box 621, Folder 78)
    - Food and Drug Administration, 1988-1991 (Box 621, Folder 79)
    - Foreign aid, Newsclips, 1991-1992 (Box 621, Folder 80)
    - Gene therapy research, 1992-1994 (Box 621, Folder 81)
    - Grassroots lobbying, 1993-1994 (Box 622, Folder 1)
    - William Gray, Newsclips, 1991 (Box 622, Folder 2)
    - Gulf crises, Newsclips, 1991 (Box 622, Folder 3)
    - Gun control, Constituent communication, 1993 (Box 622, Folder 4)
    - GQ articles, 1990 (Box 622, Folder 5)
    - Sheldon Hackery, 1993 (Box 622, Folder 6)
    - Hatch Act amednment, 1994 (Box 622, Folder 7)
    - Health center locations, 1990-1992 (Box 622, Folder 8)
    - Health PASS, 1993-1994 (Box 622, Folder 9)
    - Health publications, 1990-1992 (Box 622, Folder 10)
    - Healthcare, 1987-1993 (Box 622, Folder 11)
    - Healthcare, Chart, 1993-1994 (Box 622, Folder 12)
    - Healthcare, Contacts, 1994 (Box 622, Folder 13)
    - Healthcare, Maternity, 1992 (Box 622, Folder 14)
    - Healthcare, People with disabilities, 1994 (Box 622, Folder 15)
    - Healthcare, Plans, 1994 (Box 622, Folder 16)
    - Healthcare, Press, 1987-1993 (Box 622, Folder 17)
    - Healthcare, Public, 1990-1991 (Box 622, Folder 18)
    - Healthcare, Reform, 1994 (Box 622, Folder 19)
    - John Heinz seat, Newsclips, 1991 (Box 622, Folder 20)
    - High school student programs, 1992 (Box 622, Folder 21)
    - High speed rail, 1990 (Box 622, Folder 22)
    - Higher education funding, 1988-1992 (Box 622, Folder 23)
    - Highway bill for Pennsylvania, 1991 (Box 622, Folder 24)
    - Hispanics, Newsclips, 1991 (Box 622, Folder 25)
    - Homeless, Newsclips, 1990-1991 (Box 622, Folder 26)
    - Homeless shelter in Harrisburg, 1993 (Box 622, Folder 27)
    - Housing and Urban Development (HUD), 1992 (Box 622, Folder 28)
    - HUD, Baldwin Towers, 1994 (Box 622, Folder 29)
    - Healthcare, Minority media, 1993 (Box 622, Folder 30)
    - Healthcare, Non-profit pilot plan, Detroit, 1994 (Box 622, Folder 31)
    - Healthcare, Press, 1990-1992 (Box 622, Folder 32)
    - HIV/AIDS, Newsclips, 1990-1992 (Box 622, Folder 33)
    - Immigration, 1990 (Box 622, Folder 34)
    - Independence Hall preservation, 1990-1993 (Box 622, Folder 35)
    - Intermodal Transportation Efficiency Act, 1991 (Box 622, Folder 36)
    - International newsclips, 1990-1991 (Box 622, Folder 37)
    - IRS consolidation, 1993 (Box 622, Folder 38)
    - Issues constituents are most active on, 1994 (Box 622, Folder 39)
    - Issues, Newsclips, 1990-1992 (Box 622, Folder 40)
    - Juvenile justice, 1994 (Box 622, Folder 41)
    - JFK movie, Newsclips, 1991-1992 (Box 622, Folder 42)
    - JFK, Resolution, 1992 (Box 622, Folder 43)
    - Labor talking points, 1992 (Box 622, Folder 44)
    - Legislation, 1991 (Box 622, Folder 45)
    - Legislative procedure information, undated (Box 622, Folder 46)
    - Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual and Transgender (LGBT) protests, 1994 (Box 622, Folder 47)
    - LGBT, Rights, 1993 (Box 622, Folder 48)
    - LGBT, Rights in the military, 1993 (Box 622, Folder 49)
    - Letterkenny Army Depot, 1990 (Box 622, Folder 50)
    - Lincoln Day speech, 1993 (Box 622, Folder 51)
    - Lobbying information, 1986 (Box 622, Folder 52)
    - Logan geotechnical study, 1986 (Box 622, Folder 53)
    - Major League Baseball (MLB) antitrust, 1993 (Box 622, Folder 54)
    - Marijuana, 1993 (Box 622, Folder 55)
    - Mass transit legislation, 1986-1991 (Box 622, Folder 56)
    - Joseph McDade and Michael Baylson, Newsclips, 1992 (Box 622, Folder 57)
    - Medicaid, Drug and alcohol rehab, 1988-1994 (Box 622, Folder 58)
    - Medicare, Declogger reimbursement, 1991-1994 (Box 622, Folder 59)
    - Miami navy base closure, 1992-1993 (Box 622, Folder 60)
    - Middle East, Newsclips, 1990-1992 (Box 622, Folder 61)
    - Minimum wage, 1989 (Box 623, Folder 1)
    - Missing children, 1986 (Box 623, Folder 2)
    - Montgomery County open space preservation, 1993 (Box 623, Folder 3)
    - National Advisory Council for Environmental Policy and Technology Superfund Evaluation Committee, 1993 (Box 623, Folder 4)
    - National Center for Research Resources v. Teamsters, 1992-2993 (Box 623, Folder 5-6)
    - National crime, Newsclips, 1990-1991 (Box 623, Folder 7)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1991 (Box 623, Folder 8)
    - National health, 1990-1991 (Box 623, Folder 9)
    - National Highway System, 1994 (Box 623, Folder 10)
    - National Maritime Initiative, 1993 (Box 623, Folder 11)
    - National news, 1990-1991 (Box 623, Folder 12)
    - National Organization of Physicians Who Care, 1994 (Box 623, Folder 13)
    - National politics, Newsclips, 1990-1991 (Box 623, Folder 14)
    - Naval base closing, 1993 (Box 623, Folder 15)
    - Naval hospital, 1986-1987 (Box 623, Folder 16)
    - Naval shipyard, 1991 (Box 623, Folder 17)
    - Naval shipyard lawsuit, 1993 (Box 623, Folder 18)
    - Navy base defense conversation, 1993-1994 (Box 623, Folder 19)
    - Navy shipyard litigation, 1991-1993 (Box 623, Folder 20-21)
    - Navy yard, Reuse, 1993 (Box 623, Folder 22)
    - Navy yard, Reuse litigation, 1993-1994 (Box 623, Folder 23)
    - Navy yard, Press, 1991 (Box 623, Folder 24)
    - Nuclear Regulatory Commission and oncology treatments, 1993 (Box 623, Folder 25)
    - Nuclear waste, 1992-1994 (Box 623, Folder 26)
    - Office manual, 1985 (Box 623, Folder 27)
    - Outgoing letters of recommendation and referrals, 1993-1994 (Box 623, Folder 28)
    - Paoli rail yard, 1986-1992 (Box 623, Folder 29)
    - Peace Corps, 1990-1992 (Box 623, Folder 30)
    - Frank Pecora, 1993 (Box 623, Folder 31)
    - Pennsylvania, Budget and economy, Newsclips, 1990-1991 (Box 623, Folder 32)
    - Pennsylvania, Courts, Newsclips, 1991-1992 (Box 623, Folder 33)
    - Pennsylvania, Department of Transportation district engineers, 1983 (Box 623, Folder 34)
    - Pennsylvania, Government crime, 1994 (Box 623, Folder 35)
    - Pennsylvania, Redistricting, Newsclips, 1992 (Box 623, Folder 36)
    - Pennsylvania, Report, 1990 (Box 623, Folder 37)
    - Pennsylvania, Rules for continuing legal education, 1992 (Box 623, Folder 38)
    - Pennsylvania, Supreme Court Rolf Larson impeachment, 1994 (Box 623, Folder 39)
    - Philadelphia, Budget and economy, Newsclips, 1990-1991 (Box 623, Folder 40)
    - Philadelphia, Crime, Newsclips, 1990 (Box 623, Folder 41)
    - Philadelphia, Enterprise zones, 1993-1994 (Box 623, Folder 42)
    - Philadelphia, GAO office closing, 1993-1994 (Box 623, Folder 43)
    - Philadelphia, Health and welfare, Newsclips, 1990 (Box 624, Folder 1)
    - Philadelphia Housing Association, 1990-1991 (Box 624, Folder 2)
    - Philadelphia, Incinerator ash problems, 1987 (Box 624, Folder 3)
    - Philadelphia International Airport, 1991 (Box 624, Folder 4)
    - Philadelphia International Airport visit, 1991 (Box 624, Folder 5)
    - Philadelphia, Mayoral race, 1991 (Box 624, Folder 6)
    - Philadelphia, Politics, Newsclips, 1990-1991 (Box 624, Folder 7)
    - Philadelphia, Ports, Newsclips, 1990-1991 (Box 624, Folder 8)
    - Philadelphia, Press, 1990-1991 (Box 624, Folder 9)
    - Philadelphia, Prisons, 1991-1992 (Box 624, Folder 10)
    - Philadelphia, Prison proposals, 1994 (Box 624, Folder 11-14)
    - Philadelphia, Southeastern Pennsylvania Transportation Authority (SEPTA), 1990-1991 (Box 624, Folder 15)
    - Police, Newsclips, 1990 (Box 624, Folder 16)
    - PACs, Newsclips, 1990-1992 (Box 624, Folder 17)
    - A Presidential Salute, 1992 (Box 624, Folder 18)
    - Prisons, 1988-1992 (Box 624, Folder 19)
    - Procurement, 1988 (Box 624, Folder 20)
    - Product liability, 1994 (Box 624, Folder 21)
    - Productivity Software International, Veterans, 1993 (Box 624, Folder 22)
    - Professional sports, 1990 (Box 624, Folder 23)
    - Proposed book, undated (Box 624, Folder 24)
    - Removal of administrative law judges, 1993 (Box 624, Folder 25)
    - Midge Rendell, 1994 (Box 624, Folder 26)
    - Radon, 1985-1991 (Box 624, Folder 27)
    - Reports on Middle East trip, 1993-1994 (Box 624, Folder 28)
    - Schuylkill River Park development, 1992 (Box 624, Folder 29)
    - Senate campaign, 1992-1994 (Box 624, Folder 30)
    - Senate campaign, Absentee ballot scandal, 1992-1993 (Box 624, Folder 31)
    - Senate campaign, Barbender Cox, Political media report, undated (Box 624, Folder 32)
    - Senate campaign, Colville newsclips, 1992 (Box 624, Folder 33)
    - Senate campaign, Direct mail, 1992 (Box 624, Folder 34)
    - Senate campaign, Finances, 1993-1994 (Box 624, Folder 35)
    - Senate campaign, Financial contributions, 1992 (Box 624, Folder 36)
    - Senate campaign, Steve Freind, 1992 (Box 624, Folder 37)
    - Senate campaign, Freddie Mann Friedman, 1992 (Box 624, Folder 38)
    - Senate campaign, Press, 1991 (Box 624, Folder 39)
    - Senate campaign, Press, 1992 (Box 624, Folder 40)
    - Senate campaign, Republican National Convention (RNC) events, 1992 (Box 625, Folder 1)
    - Senate campaign, Sample lease, 1992 (Box 625, Folder 2)
    - Senate campaign, Mark Singel, 1992 (Box 625, Folder 3)
    - Senate campaign, Arlen Specter, 1992 (Box 625, Folder 4-5)
    - Senate campaign, Dick Thornburgh, 1992 (Box 625, Folder 6)
    - Senate campaign, Philip Valenti, 1992 (Box 625, Folder 7)
    - Senate campaign, Victory '92 payment to Eagle, 1992 (Box 625, Folder 8)
    - Senate campaign, Voting analysis, 1992-1993 (Box 625, Folder 9)
    - Senate campaign, Lynn Yeakel, 1992 (Box 625, Folder 10)
    - Senate pay raise, 1990-1992 (Box 625, Folder 11)
    - Senate races, 1990-1991 (Box 625, Folder 12)
    - Social Security in the Federal Budget, 1990 (Box 625, Folder 13)
    - Social Security notch babies, undated (Box 625, Folder 14)
    - Societ republics, Newsclips, 1991 (Box 625, Folder 15)
    - Spectacor new arena, 1991 (Box 625, Folder 16)
    - Staff, 1990 (Box 625, Folder 17)
    - Steamtown Roundhouse and Turntable, 1990 (Box 625, Folder 18)
    - Strikebreaker laws, 1994 (Box 625, Folder 19)
    - Superfund sites, 1988-1992 (Box 625, Folder 20)
    - Supreme Court decisions, 1990-1992 (Box 625, Folder 21)
    - Supreme Court nomination process, 1988 (Box 625, Folder 22)
    - Supreme Court nominations, Newsclips, 1990-1992 (Box 625, Folder 23)
    - Toxic waste sites list, 1985 (Box 625, Folder 24)
    - Trade, Japan, 1990-1992 (Box 625, Folder 25)
    - Transportation, Analysis by the Commonwealth Foundation, 1988 (Box 625, Folder 26)
    - Transportation, Appropriations, 1993 (Box 625, Folder 27)
    - Transportation, Newsclips, 1991 (Box 625, Folder 28)
    - Travel, Open houses, Appearances in Pennsylvania, 1981-1990 (Box 625, Folder 29-30)
    - Urban Agenda Act, 1994 (Box 625, Folder 31)
    - US Army Corps of Engineers, 1991 (Box 625, Folder 32)
    - US Fish and Wildlife Service appropriations, 1988 (Box 625, Folder 33)
    - Used car price increase, 1994 (Box 625, Folder 34)
    - USPCI, 1993 (Box 625, Folder 35)
    - Veterans Affairs, 1988-1992 (Box 625, Folder 36)
    - V-22 Osprey, 1990-1992 (Box 625, Folder 37)
    - Waste Management, 1990-1991 (Box 625, Folder 38)
    - Webster v. Reproductive Health Services, 1989 (Box 625, Folder 39)
    - Women's and family issues, Newsclips, 1990-1991 (Box 625, Folder 40)
  - Paul Michel, 1981-1987; 24.
    Paul Michel served as administrative assistant, 1982-1986.
    - Affirmative action, 1985-1986 (Box 625, Folder 41)
    - Agriculture, undated (Box 625, Folder 42)
    - Anti-ballistic Missile (ABM) Treaty, 1987 (Box 626, Folder 1-4)
    - Career criminals, 1986-1988 (Box 626, Folder 5)
    - Chronological files, January-March 1982 (Box 626, Folder 6)
    - Chronological files, April 1982, January-February 1983 (Box 626, Folder 7)
    - Chronological files, March-April 1983 (Box 626, Folder 8)
    - Chronological files, May 1983 (Box 626, Folder 9)
    - Chronological files, May-June 1983 (Box 626, Folder 10)
    - Chronological files, June-July 1983 (Box 626, Folder 11)
    - Chronological files, July 1983 (Box 626, Folder 12)
    - Chronological files, August 1983 (Box 626, Folder 13)
    - Chronological files, August-October 1983 (Box 627, Folder 1)
    - Chronological files, November 1983 (Box 627, Folder 2)
    - Chronological files, December 1983 (Box 627, Folder 3)
    - Courthourses, 1984-1986 (Box 627, Folder 4)
    - Court stripping, 1982-1985 (Box 627, Folder 5)
    - Criminal forfeiture, 1983-1985 (Box 627, Folder 6)
    - Defense fraud, 1984-1985 (Box 627, Folder 7-8)
    - Football compromise bill, 1985-1986 (Box 627, Folder 9-11)
    - Israel and Lebanon trip, 1982 (Box 627, Folder 12)
    - Legislation, 1981-1982 (Box 627, Folder 13)
    - Legislation, Career Criminals Act, Background, 1981 (Box 627, Folder 14-15)
    - Legislation, Career Criminals Act, Hearing, 1981 (Box 627, Folder 16)
    - Memos, Steve Irwin, 1983 (Box 628, Folder 1)
    - Memos, Lee Malcolm, Kevin Mills, Elizabeth Montgomery, 1983 (Box 628, Folder 2)
    - Memos, Iris Portnoy, 1983 (Box 628, Folder 3)
    - Memos, Iris Portnoy, Suzanne Spaulding, Lonnie Taylor, 1983-1984 (Box 628, Folder 4)
    - Office, 1982-1984 (Box 628, Folder 5-6)
    - Op-ed, Busing, 1981 (Box 628, Folder 7)
    - Personal, 1982 (Box 628, Folder 8)
    - Presidential Protection Commission, 1981 (Box 628, Folder 9-10)
  - Elizabeth Montgomery, 1981-1982; 25.
    Elizabeth Montgomery served as staff assistant, 1981-1984.
    - Bills and statements, 1981-1982 (Box 628, Folder 11-12)
    - Memos to Specter returned, 1981 (Box 628, Folder 13-14)
    - Northeast-Midwest Congressional Coalition, 1981 (Box 628, Folder 15)
    - Northeast-Midwest Congressional Coalition, 1981 (Box 629, Folder 1-2)
    - Social Security, 1982 (Box 629, Folder 3-8)
  - Sylvia Nolde, 1981-1984; 26.
    Sylvia Nolde served as: staff assistant, 1981-1984; appointments secretary, 1985-1991; and special assistant, 1992-1994.
    - Schedule, March 1981 (Box 629, Folder 9)
    - Schedule, September 1981 (Box 629, Folder 10-11)
    - Schedule, 1981-1982 (Box 629, Folder 12)
    - Schedule, February 1982 (Box 629, Folder 13)
    - Schedule, May 1982 (Box 629, Folder 14)
    - Schedule, July 1982 (Box 629, Folder 15)
    - Schedule, August 1982 (Box 630, Folder 1-2)
    - Schedule, October 1982 (Box 630, Folder 3-4)
    - Schedule, November 1982 (Box 630, Folder 5)
    - Schedule, January 1983 (Box 630, Folder 6-7)
    - Schedule, February-March 1983 (Box 630, Folder 8)
    - Schedule, April 1983 (Box 630, Folder 9)
    - Schedule, May-June 1983 (Box 630, Folder 10)
    - Schedule, July-September 1983 (Box 630, Folder 11)
    - Schedule, September-October 1983 (Box 630, Folder 12)
    - Schedule, October 1983 (Box 630, Folder 13)
    - Schedule, December 1983 (Box 630, Folder 14)
    - Schedule, 1983 (Box 630, Folder 15)
    - Schedule, February 1984 (Box 630, Folder 16)
    - Schedule, April 1984 (Box 631, Folder 1)
    - Telephone logs, 1981-1984 (Box 631, Folder 2)
  - Yvonne O'Connor, 1981-1996; 27.
    Yvonne O'Connor served as executive director, Pittsburgh office, 1990-1997.
    - Pittsburgh trip files, May 1981-March 1982 (Box 631, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, April 1982 (Box 631, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, June-July 1982 (Box 631, Folder 5)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, August-September 1982 (Box 631, Folder 6)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, October 1982 (Box 631, Folder 7)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, January-February 1983 (Box 631, Folder 8)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, March-April 1983 (Box 631, Folder 9)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, April-May 1983 (Box 631, Folder 10)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, June-July 1983 (Box 631, Folder 11)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, August 1983 (Box 631, Folder 12)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, September-October 1983 (Box 631, Folder 13)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, October 1983 (Box 632, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, November-December 1983 (Box 632, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, January-March 1984 (Box 632, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, April-June 1984 (Box 632, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, July-September 1984 (Box 632, Folder 5)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, October 1984 (Box 632, Folder 6-7)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, November 1984-January 1985 (Box 632, Folder 8)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, February 1986 (Box 632, Folder 9)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, March 1986 (Box 632, Folder 10)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, April 1986 (Box 632, Folder 11)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, May 1986 (Box 632, Folder 12)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, June 1986 (Box 632, Folder 13)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, July 1986 (Box 632, Folder 14)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, July 1986 (Box 633, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, July-August 1986 (Box 633, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, September 1986 (Box 633, Folder 3-5)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, October 1986 (Box 633, Folder 6-8)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, November-December 1986 (Box 633, Folder 9)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, January0February 1987 (Box 633, Folder 10)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, March 1987 (Box 633, Folder 11)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, April 1987 (Box 633, Folder 12)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, May-June 1987 (Box 633, Folder 13)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, July 1987 (Box 634, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, August-September 1987 (Box 634, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, October-November 1987 (Box 634, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, December 1987-January 1988 (Box 634, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, March 1988 (Box 634, Folder 5-6)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, April 1988 (Box 634, Folder 7)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, May 1988 (Box 634, Folder 8)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, June-July 1988 (Box 634, Folder 9)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, July 1988 (Box 634, Folder 10)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, August-September 1988 (Box 634, Folder 11)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, October 1988 (Box 634, Folder 12)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, November 1988 (Box 635, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, December 1988 (Box 635, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, January 1989 (Box 635, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, February 1989 (Box 635, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, March 1989 (Box 635, Folder 5)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, April 1989 (Box 635, Folder 6)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, April-May 1989 (Box 635, Folder 7)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, May-June 1989 (Box 635, Folder 8)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, June 1989 (Box 635, Folder 9)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, July 1989 (Box 635, Folder 10)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, August 1989 (Box 635, Folder 11-12)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, August-September 1989 (Box 636, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, October-November 1989 (Box 636, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, November 1989 (Box 636, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, December 1989 (Box 636, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, February-March 1990 (Box 636, Folder 5)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, March-April 1990 (Box 636, Folder 6)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, May 1990 (Box 636, Folder 7)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, June 1990 (Box 636, Folder 8)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, July 1990 (Box 636, Folder 9)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, August-September 1990 (Box 636, Folder 10)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, October-December 1990 (Box 636, Folder 11)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, January-February 1991 (Box 636, Folder 12)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, March-April 1991 (Box 636, Folder 13)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, April 1991 (Box 637, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, May 1991 (Box 637, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, June 1991 (Box 637, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, July 1991 (Box 637, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, July-August 1991 (Box 637, Folder 5)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, September 1991 (Box 637, Folder 6)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, October-December 1991 (Box 637, Folder 7)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, January-February 1992 (Box 637, Folder 8)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, February 1992 (Box 637, Folder 9)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, March 1992 (Box 637, Folder 10)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, April-May 1992 (Box 637, Folder 11)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, June-July 1992 (Box 637, Folder 12)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, July 1992 (Box 637, Folder 13)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, July 1992 (Box 638, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, August 1992 (Box 638, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, September 1992 (Box 638, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, October 1992 (Box 638, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, November 1992-April 1993 (Box 638, Folder 5)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, June-October 1993 (Box 638, Folder 6)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, December 1983 (Box 638, Folder 7)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, January-July 1994 (Box 638, Folder 8)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, August-October 1994 (Box 638, Folder 9)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, December 1994-February 1995 (Box 638, Folder 10)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, March 1995 (Box 638, Folder 11)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, May-June 1995 (Box 638, Folder 12)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, September-October 1995 (Box 639, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, November 1995-February 1996 (Box 639, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, March 1996 (Box 639, Folder 3-4)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, April 1996 (Box 639, Folder 5)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, May 1996 (Box 639, Folder 6)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, May-August 1996 (Box 639, Folder 7)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, September-October 1996 (Box 639, Folder 8)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, November-December 1996 (Box 639, Folder 9)
  - Anna Platt, 2006-2007; 28.
    Anna Platt served as: staff assistant, 2007-2008; assistant to the chief of staff, 2008-2009; and legislative correspondent, 2009-2010.
    - Assistance to Firefighters grant, 2006 (Box 639, Folder 10)
    - Assistance to Firefighters grant, 2007 (Box 639, Folder 11-12)
  - Patricia Root, 1983-1996; 29.
    Patricia Root served as: executive director, Allentown office, 1982; and executive director, Erie office, 1983-1997.
    - Memos, August 1983 (Box 639, Folder 13)
    - Memos, April 1984 (Box 639, Folder 14)
    - Memos, July 1984 (Box 639, Folder 15)
    - Memos, October 1986 (Box 639, Folder 16)
    - Schedule, 1983 (Box 639, Folder 17)
    - Schedule, April 1983 (Box 639, Folder 18)
    - Schedule, August 1983 (Box 639, Folder 19)
    - Schedule, April 1984 (Box 640, Folder 1)
    - Schedule, June 1984 (Box 640, Folder 2)
    - Schedule, July 1984 (Box 640, Folder 3)
    - Schedule, October 1984 (Box 640, Folder 4)
    - Schedule, March 1985 (Box 640, Folder 5)
    - Schedule, April 1985 (Box 640, Folder 6)
    - Schedule, May 1985 (Box 640, Folder 7)
    - Schedule, August 1985 (Box 640, Folder 8)
    - Schedule, February 1986 (Box 640, Folder 9)
    - Schedule, March 1986 (Box 640, Folder 10)
    - Schedule, May 1986 (Box 640, Folder 11)
    - Schedule, July 1986 (Box 640, Folder 12)
    - Schedule, September 1986 (Box 640, Folder 13)
    - Schedule, October 1986 (Box 640, Folder 14)